[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Would it be too far, Mr. Welch, to go out and say he was the greatest CEO of our time, maybe ever?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "be", "too", "far", ",", "Mr.", "Welch", ",", "to", "go", "out", "and", "say", "he", "was", "the", "greatest", "CEO", "of", "our", "time", ",", "maybe", "ever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, I -- you know somebody might argue with you on that, but I'd have trouble finding anyone better.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "you", "know", "somebody", "might", "argue", "with", "you", "on", "that", ",", "but", "I", "'d", "have", "trouble", "finding", "anyone", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Welch"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "So the question is, how is this going to affect Apple products down the road?", "question_tokens": ["So", "the", "question", "is", ",", "how", "is", "this", "going", "to", "affect", "Apple", "products", "down", "the", "road", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "That is the big question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "the", "big", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "In a word or two, what would you think his legacy is going to be?", "question_tokens": ["In", "a", "word", "or", "two", ",", "what", "would", "you", "think", "his", "legacy", "is", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "CD", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I think he's just -- you know, he was a marketing genius.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "just", "--", "you", "know", ",", "he", "was", "a", "marketing", "genius", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "How great of a leader, Steve, was he?", "question_tokens": ["How", "great", "of", "a", "leader", ",", "Steve", ",", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I really wrote that piece because when Steve Jobs got sick there was a lot of discussion about how great a leader he was.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "wrote", "that", "piece", "because", "when", "Steve", "Jobs", "got", "sick", "there", "was", "a", "lot", "of", "discussion", "about", "how", "great", "a", "leader", "he", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fitzgerald"], "PERSON": ["F. Scott Fitzgerald", "Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "How did he do that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "he", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Well, you know, F. Scott Fitzgerald said there are no second acts in American lives and Steve Jobs proved Fitzgerald wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "F.", "Scott", "Fitzgerald", "said", "there", "are", "no", "second", "acts", "in", "American", "lives", "and", "Steve", "Jobs", "proved", "Fitzgerald", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What was he like in those days?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "in", "those", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "He was -- you know what, he was always interested in every technical, electronic gadget there was in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "--", "you", "know", "what", ",", "he", "was", "always", "interested", "in", "every", "technical", ",", "electronic", "gadget", "there", "was", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Who would have been more successful if you hadn't met each other?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "have", "been", "more", "successful", "if", "you", "had", "n't", "met", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Steve Jobs, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Steve", "Jobs", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "You're still an Apple employee, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "still", "an", "Apple", "employee", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I am still an Apple employee.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "still", "an", "Apple", "employee", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "How much do you get?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "get", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I think the check -- I don't even see it, but I think it's a couple hundred bucks every two weeks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "check", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "even", "see", "it", ",", "but", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "couple", "hundred", "bucks", "every", "two", "weeks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Do you have a stake in the company at all these days?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "stake", "in", "the", "company", "at", "all", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "My wife and I really aren't big stock traders.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "wife", "and", "I", "really", "are", "n't", "big", "stock", "traders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "In terms of what you know of him, what do you think he'd like the legacy to be, the Steve Jobs legacy to be?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "what", "you", "know", "of", "him", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'d", "like", "the", "legacy", "to", "be", ",", "the", "Steve", "Jobs", "legacy", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Giving mankind the most useful, helpful tools we've ever had in our history, the ones we would enjoy the most, the ones that we not only use but we love, that we come to love, like a human being.", "answer_tokens": ["Giving", "mankind", "the", "most", "useful", ",", "helpful", "tools", "we", "'ve", "ever", "had", "in", "our", "history", ",", "the", "ones", "we", "would", "enjoy", "the", "most", ",", "the", "ones", "that", "we", "not", "only", "use", "but", "we", "love", ",", "that", "we", "come", "to", "love", ",", "like", "a", "human", "being", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Was the computer, in which you were very instrumental in producing -- is that going to be the greatest invention of, you know, the last millennium?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "the", "computer", ",", "in", "which", "you", "were", "very", "instrumental", "in", "producing", "--", "is", "that", "going", "to", "be", "the", "greatest", "invention", "of", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "last", "millennium", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "It's hard to say.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "And they should be out playing Conquers (ph) and soccer and stuff like that, shouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["And", "they", "should", "be", "out", "playing", "Conquers", "(", "ph", ")", "and", "soccer", "and", "stuff", "like", "that", ",", "should", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "I don't think we could stop the effect of the future, the future we created giving them devices.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "could", "stop", "the", "effect", "of", "the", "future", ",", "the", "future", "we", "created", "giving", "them", "devices", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What goes through your mind on this sad day?", "question_tokens": ["What", "goes", "through", "your", "mind", "on", "this", "sad", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "You know, we were so prepared for this.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "were", "so", "prepared", "for", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Or was he simply focused on technology?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "he", "simply", "focused", "on", "technology", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Steve was very focused.", "answer_tokens": ["Steve", "was", "very", "focused", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Did you get to know him a little bit?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "to", "know", "him", "a", "little", "bit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "I met him, but I really never had a chance to actually interview him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "met", "him", ",", "but", "I", "really", "never", "had", "a", "chance", "to", "actually", "interview", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "What is going to happen to Apple, Andy, now that Steve Jobs unfortunately has passed away?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "to", "happen", "to", "Apple", ",", "Andy", ",", "now", "that", "Steve", "Jobs", "unfortunately", "has", "passed", "away", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Well, there's been a lot of speculation about that for a long time, Wolf.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "been", "a", "lot", "of", "speculation", "about", "that", "for", "a", "long", "time", ",", "Wolf", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"], "PERSON": ["Andy", "Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "And I think you're in this business now because of him, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "in", "this", "business", "now", "because", "of", "him", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What's happening over there, Susan?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "happening", "over", "there", ",", "Susan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Wolf, it's also a busy place here as people who admired Steve Jobs are stopping by, leaving flowers and a few hand made signs as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Wolf", ",", "it", "'s", "also", "a", "busy", "place", "here", "as", "people", "who", "admired", "Steve", "Jobs", "are", "stopping", "by", ",", "leaving", "flowers", "and", "a", "few", "hand", "made", "signs", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "How did you hear about the death?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "about", "the", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "I got a Tweet from my friend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "a", "Tweet", "from", "my", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "What attracted you -- that won't change, I should say -- but what attracted you to Steve Jobs and to the Apple products?", "question_tokens": ["What", "attracted", "you", "--", "that", "wo", "n't", "change", ",", "I", "should", "say", "--", "but", "what", "attracted", "you", "to", "Steve", "Jobs", "and", "to", "the", "Apple", "products", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "CC", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "It was just simplicity overall.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "just", "simplicity", "overall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"], "PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111005pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "You bought your first Apple product at what age?", "question_tokens": ["You", "bought", "your", "first", "Apple", "product", "at", "what", "age", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: At 14.", "answer_tokens": ["NIDENTIFIED", "MALE", ":", "At", "14", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]